(Howard:)When the Mars rover
started pulling to the left...
...I performed a front-end alignment
from 62 million miles away.
(Howard:)No, that baby's broken.
LEONARD:
Come on, guys, push.
HOWARD: If I push any harder,
I'm gonna give birth to my colon.
RAJESH:
I can't feel my fingers. Hurry up.
(Sheldon:)It's the same amount of work,
no matter how fast you go. Basic physics.
RAJESH: Sheldon.
- Yeah?
RAJESH: If my fingers ever work again,
I've got a job for the middle one.
- Oh, hey, guys.
- Hi, Penny.
[RAJESH AND HOWARD SCREAM]
(Leonard(letting go of time machine, as does Sheldon):)Take a break, guys.
- What are you doing?
- Just moving something upstairs.
- What is it?
- Just, you know, a time machine.
(Penny:)Okay, neat.
But I really gotta get to work.